{
    "subject": "resource/Leona_Lewis",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Leona Lewis",
    "human_readable": "The name of Leona Lewis is Leona Lewis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.971217691898346,
            "question": "Is 'Leona Lewis' a commonly known name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9563462138175964,
            "question": "What is the full name of Leona Lewis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.917113184928894,
            "question": "Is 'Leona Lewis' a unique name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8978535532951355,
            "question": "Does Leona Lewis have a stage name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8669784069061279,
            "question": "Is Leona Lewis a famous person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8644994497299194,
            "question": "What could be some possible nicknames for someone named Leona Lewis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7877694368362427,
            "question": "Are there any famous individuals with similar names to Leona Lewis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6069189310073853,
            "question": "Could 'Leona Lewis' be the title of a song or book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5948329567909241,
            "question": "What type of profession does Leona Lewis have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48009929060935974,
            "question": "Has Leona Lewis achieved recognition in her field?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Leona Lewis is Leona Lewis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8688_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of profession does Leona Lewis have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8688_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could 'Leona Lewis' be the title of a song or book?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8688_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous individuals with similar names to Leona Lewis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8688_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8688_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer aligns with the provided documents which consistently refer to the individual as \"Leona Lewis\" without any discrepancy in her name."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}